Narrator: 1
F: I can’t afford a new car, it’s going to have to be second-hand.
Narrator: 2
F: Despite being nearly 93, my mum is incredibly youthful.
Narrator: 3
M: I’ve never heard a singing voice like Sally’s – she has a totally original talent.
Narrator: 4
M: During the Second World War, thrifty shoppers could make a little money go a long way.
Narrator: 5
F: I wouldn’t get that dress - it looks really cheap, as if it would fall apart after one wash.
Narrator: 6
M: I know he’s probably trying to be nice, but I find him a bit smarmy.
Narrator: 7
F: I’m making a determined effort to give up eating chocolate.
Narrator: 8
M: They launched an aggressive advertising campaign intended to annihilate the competition.